Developers spend hours inside the same work surface.
Most themes are either too limited, or they cover the workspace,
break layout, and add background overhead.
Codex Dream Skin makes Codex personal without sacrificing
readability, stability, or control.
The workflow starts with a visual brief.
Codex and GPT-5.6 organize color, backgrounds,
original Image2 mecha-cat variants, semantic icons, and animation.
Every item has a role, version, release status,
and publication boundary.
This is not a static wallpaper.
The theme is split into independent background, character,
glass-surface, button, and interaction modules.
Tests and payload budgets run first. Then a local CDP one-shot
applies modules without patching the official app.
After activation, native functions remain intact.
The left navigation uses dimensional,
semantic cat-inspired icons.
The background preserves a readable work-safe area.